Pounding, pounding, pounding
Pitter-patter-patter
pound pound pound
pound, pound, pound
Good morning.
I'm just setting up the camera.
Number one.
Orange juice.
It's delicious.
I came up with the hairstyles for all the members today.
This one goes a little forward.
I like the first one.
Look how slow it's going.
Her smile is so slow!
Looks like Julia and Ah-chan bought it for me!
Siren post
Good luck today!
Good morning!
The staff came to see us.
Good morning.
As of noon today.
In preparation
Anko
of Kocian and Chillian.
I bought matcha green tea and
I would like to eat chocolate
I'd like you all to take a look.
Is there anything unusual?
Good night.
Chocolate maple manjuu
Toritomo Chocolate
Get it!
Good morning
Today, it's Shimome Chaseji
I got Momiji-manju!
Yoo-hoo!
There were 6 kinds of Momiji-manju.
There were six kinds, but they were all gone!
Follow me, follow me, follow me, follow me
Lucky, he's not feeling well... and then it's over
Yay!
My eyelashes are done!
I forgot my hat today and my sleeping habits are a little bad, no?
Today, we're celebrating a staff member's birthday.
We love surprises, that's why we do it all the time
We're celebrating the day of the staff member who edits Takehara!
I'm looking forward to it
I got a Gomijimanju!
Volume 1, 2nd one
2 calories from the beginning
Two from the start
Okay, I got it!
Good morning
I brought you some hot water.
Just now.
Oh, I brought hot water.
I've been eating Momiji-manju since this morning.
I bought some cheese momiji-manjyu as a souvenir when I arrived.
I ate it first, but then I got a fresh momiji-manju as a gift.
I just ate the green tea one!
It was so soft and doughy!
It was delicious! I ate it right away!
Today's haircut was produced by Hitaka, who decided on the haircut she wanted everyone to have.
I haven't had this haircut in a while.
It's been a long time.
It's been a while since I've had this haircut.
Yoo-hoo!
Hello.
Today.
It's a tree in Pearney.
I came all the way to Hiroshima
I came all the way to Hiroshima!
Hello, this is Pianney.
Wow, what a surprise!
What? When?
Taninon
Hi, Hiyori.
Hiyori, I'm here for love.
Thank you. I'm here, love.
I came to see Hiyori. I came.
Wait, don't tell me I don't have Hiyori's hair.
I came to see Hiyori today.
Thank you. It's cute.
But maybe I look better.
I don't think so.
I don't know. Which one would look better in an advertisement?
It's true. This hairstyle.
It's cute.
I knew it. It looks good on you.
Thank you.
Look at Kananan.
I bought this souvenir yesterday.
Looks delicious!
Kaki soy sauce.
Potato snacks.
I like it.
You didn't buy it?
No, I didn't.
I was just looking at all the delicious-looking things you bought.
I bought soy sauce.Because I bought soy sauce.
So.
I bought various souvenirs.
I bought a lot yesterday.
I mean, I got this one.
You brought it?
Kogimu!
That has nothing to do with this.
It doesn't matter at all.
It's cute.
The people around me didn't see what Kogimu made.
But I found it and bought it. It's so cute.
And so is the container.
Look at it. It's so cute.
There are so many kinds.
They are so cute.
I think I'll put it on my drink.
Drinks?
I'm thinking of putting it on my stage drink to get power.
I'm thinking about it.
This park seems to be a good place for people.
I want one.
Cute.
Crackle.
No, it's not.
Which one's eating?
Crunchy-crunchy.
It's cute.
The size is the same.
Big?
Kanami is today, and my friend Kanami?
She's closed today.
Really? I don't know why I'm not closed.
You're a hard worker.
Come with Ella and Ellie.
We're going to have okonomiyaki.
Oh, yeah.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
We used to come here all the time for okonomiyaki.
It's delicious.
I had teppan-yaki.
It was delicious.
Delicious!
Everything at home is delicious!
Great!
I love you, I say I love you. Just a little bit. Be love.
Love
love
you
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Call out. Let's do it this time.
Wobble, wobble, wobble, wobble, wobble
Shake, shake, shake, shake
I love you
Yay!
I'm not supposed to know where I'm going to come in here, right?
It changes every time, right?
It's not a spoiler, right?
Welcome.
Ah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
I like, like, like, like...
Kaki-kaki-kaki, kaki-kaki, kaki-kaki
This is also everyone's thing, Kaki.
Huh? Huh? With the comments?
Is it the same?
I'm a little confused by the form knuckle.
Oh, that's it. Persimmon? You said persimmon?
That's right. Aki-chan told me too, but she said persimmon at all.
I'll make this time's phone a sunbunyan original, as long as it has bread in it.
I hope you enjoy it every time, though.
He enjoyed it.
Third place.
Anne.
Here comes Ann.
Hey, Anne.
Ms. Ann.
Oh, my God.
She's here. She's on the staff.
I was here for the staff.
He said it's Spring at Fuyugu.
Kanamiyu.
Hanami.
Hiyomiyomiyo
mew mew mew
good night!
So cute!
Cute! Today I got strength from Pochakko and Koshimin
Give me your hand
This looks like PiyoThis is piyo-ish
I can't use that cute little thing.
You can't use something that cute!
It's okay.
Yay live points!
It's really good.
It's so cute!
Deka
De de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de de
That's great!
Do this and start taking pictures.
It's so cute!
This makes me feel so good.
So cute!
Advenker.
It's raining.
Cute, cute, cute.
Hello, everyone.
I just finished my hair and makeup. Yay.
There's something... lots of things... to eat today.
I went to Hiroshima.
Now I'm in Hiroshima, eating all kinds of delicious food.
I've been energized.
Just the other day...
I got my first pair of glasses!
I wanted a pair of glasses with UV protection and blue light protection.
But my eyes are usually very good in spring
So I went to an eyeglass shop.
But I couldn't understand a single thing
I couldn't understand a single thing
So I went to MUJI and bought a pair of glasses.
Sunglasses with blue light cut and UV protection
I bought the sunglasses.
I put them on.
But, you know, with the glasses and the mask and the headphones...
I look like a smart guy.
Okay.
Okay, well, I'm going to quiz you on that when I introduce myself today.
Here's a question. I recently debuted a certain something.
What is it? You'll never guess. I don't have bad eyesight and I don't wear glasses.
I do a lot of editing and stuff, so I'm exposed to a lot of blue light.
So I bought a pair of glasses.
I'm going to rehearsal in a few days.
I'm going to eat and get ready for rehearsal!
Bye bye!
I heard that Hiroshima has shirunashi tantanmen (noodles without soup).
I want to eat soupless tantanmen!
I also want to eat oysters!
Hi!
It's so acorny and curtainy!
Chish.
Oh, man.
What's that? This is bad.
This is bad.
It looks good.
Momiji Momomi
It's so big today. The venue.
The seats are all on top of each other, so it's really easy to see.
Oh my god, I'm breathless.
Guys!
What's this?
What's that?
Onigiri!
Ume kelp.
I was in the mood.
Oshinko? Shinko?
Shiso!
Good morning.
What's so good about it?
I knew I ate here before.
It's called oshinko.
Mericle maple
Today is the Momiji manju festival.
Which one do you want?
Which one do you want, Yuki-chan?
I'm going to go with
Shibakan
I'll try it.
What should I do?
Take your time.
I timed it right.
What shall I do?
What kind of food do you have?
Pickles?
Let's try it.
Let's ask Takuan.
What?
Isn't this a bad idea?
What's he talking about?
I'll go eat.
Omusubi Musashi.
Exquisite saltiness,
Yuden sauce and crispy nori seaweed,
The simple omusubi are handmade one by one.
It is a taste of Hiroshima that has been loved for a long time.
It tastes like oshinko.
Bon appétit.
Mmm!Yum!
Delicious!
The seaweed is delicious. It's so good.
This is so delicious!
Huh!
That's it!
It's probably takuan.
Delicious!
Whoo-hoo!
Omusubi looks delicious!
Delicious!
It fell out of my voice!
Yummy!
How do you make this?
They are so good! It's delicious! Really!
Wagyu beef is delicious! Thank you!
The musubi musashi is a hit with...
The musubi musashi is very popular among the members.
Thank you very much!
Fresh momiji wanju.
I ate two of these a while ago, and they were so delicious.
Really delicious.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Oh my God, the rice balls were delicious.
I had the ume (plum) one, and it was really good.
Ume is really good.
Is the dick bad too?
Everything is bad. This one.
It's delicious.
I don't know, the seaweed is delicious.
The rice was kind of seasoned, too.
Everything was delicious.
Today we had pudding cake.
It's really good.
What are you going to do?
I'll do my best.
Musashi. I'll never change to Musashi.
I'm going to buri Shizuoka.
Ptachyuptachyuptachyuptachyuptachyuptachyup.
I'll do it my way.
I'll get it.
Really delicious this. It's so delicious.
It's no different from Musashi.
Ew!
What? This?
This? This is amazing!
Oh, my God!
Go, go, go, go!
Go for it! Please, please, please, please!
Please, please, please, please!
Please help me out!
ivestyle
Oh, wow. We have ice cream.
Really, you can eat ice cream.
Thanks for your hard work.
Good work.
Is it a look-alike?
You look exactly the same, but your face is a little bit smaller.
You look just like him.
Bashoi bashoi bashoi.
Doerge.
Bashoi bashoi.
Juyo.
Bashoi.
It's light, I knew it. As expected.
As expected. As expected.
Self-praise.
Midosie.
Cute.
Is she here?
Hey, sis.
You're so bright.
I'd like to go alone.
Peace Memorial Park.
Where is everyone?
We're at the Ouken River.
Can we both do it at the same time?
Okay, here we go.
It's so small.
Oh, blue! Blue!
They're both blue.
Oh, that's a special prize.
Oh, really?
Oh, I dropped it.
I'm so happy!
Who's that?
Oh, it's Horchan.
My husband has to get it out.
It's Julia!
What? That's amazing!
Wow, you're the best.
Oh, she's so cute.
It's Julia!It's Julia!
That's what I'm talking about.
It's really Julia!
That's amazing.
Is that an AI?
It's AI. Yes, it's AI.
This is AI, isn't it?
Paintings, paintings, paintings, paintings, paintings, paintings, paintings, paintings...
It's so cute!
Please rattle around, everyone!
Wow, it's a real Julia!
Amazing!
Yay!
What is this?
I can use PayPay, it's so convenient!
That's great!
It's pretty good, isn't it? Gotou!
If it's red, you get this clear file.
If it's red, here it is!
We got a blue one.
Very convenient, clear file!
Hito-chan's pose is a bit confusing
Oh, great, that's great!
A little bit of an unfamiliar pose, like the law of framing
Framing
What is it?
This pose is a little difficult to imitate.
I'm not supposed to open it, but if it were green, it would look like this.
It's tapestry, isn't it?
It's surprisingly large.
When you put it in a room, it brightens up the atmosphere of the room at once.
Are you doing it?
Put it on the door like this.
Do you do that?
Noren
I use Nenemo.
Yes, I do.
If it's black, it's very tasteful.
It's perfect for this season.
It's perfect for the season. It's very tasteful.
It's got this rubber band to keep it from opening.
Mr. Neng, you can use this to tell rakugo stories in your free time before the show starts.
Yes, I mean...
Hello.
Voice.
Voice?
Yes, yes, yes.
Use your voice.
Soupless noodle soup in Hiroshima
Sense can be used for all kinds of things.
Yes, use it!
Wow!
If you get the silver one, you'll win this color paper.
It's freshly written.
I always write in the morning.
I write them at the school after I arrive at the venue.
It's freshly written.
I'll be able to do it again today.
If you get a lot of hits...
I can do it.
Please win and take them home with you!
Is he cute?
You're too cute.
I'm glad to hear that.
May we meet again in Hiroshima!
Take care of Snarky!
I love you!
It's been a long time since I've seen you in Hiroshima.
Acrylic rack!
How do you use this?
Acrylic racks...
Key chain?
There's no key chain, but it's a nice thing to have, and if you shorten it a little bit, you can hang it.
Yes, you can hang key rings or whatever you want to call them, or whatever you want to call them, or whatever you want to call them.
It's good for the "hang it, push it, win it" corner.
Please put it down, Julia's not here anymore, so please bring Oharu-chan home with you.
I don't mind if you start with "Go for it!
I'd like to be told "clang clang".
I wonder what prize would make her clang, clang, clang.
If I win gold and silver, it'll be "clang clang." It's rather effective.
I think I've heard that before. Clang, clang, clang.
Good luck with that.
You can do it by just popping in your ID and payment.
Please come and visit us at our booth! During the show, if you could wave it like this, it will stand out because it's so big.
Yes, it's cute!
It's so cute!
Please use it!
This is also perfect for summer.
It might be a little cold in winter. It might be a little cold in winter.
In summer,
But,
It's just right to appeal to your guess.
Yes, it is.
By all means, please use it.
Please come and see it.
T-shirts and stuff.
That's right.It's true!
Everyone, please make your own wet-nurses.
Make her the happiest in the world.
That's right.
She's probably the happiest person in the world right now.
Don't let her take off her skirt so that you won't lose to her.
I've never made her take off her skirt.
I've never had her take off her skirt.
She slept with me last night, and I think she's the happiest.
Please give her a proper hairdryer or something.
Yesterday, you know, something like that,
It was in your room,
What?
Oh, I did it.
I'll spray you all over.
I'll make sure it smells good,
Make sure he smells nice.
We ate okonomiyaki together,
I thought it might smell bad,
So I sprayed him with deodorant spray.
That's great.
Well, goodbye.
Bye-bye.
Aura changes with your breath, everyone,
Aura is something that comes with you.
So, be aware of it from the bottom of your body,
If you breathe with the awareness of promotion, promotion, promotion,
Aura will come naturally,
I am going to live my life with this in mind.
I hear it is good for your health.
Let's all breathe with an accelerated mind.
See you soon!
I put on my hair ornament.
A round and round bun.
Okay, I got one of these.
I'll take an onigiri.
Oshinko that seems to be the most popular!
I'm off to get Onami-kun's oshinko!
Tawara omusubi
Tawaramusubi
This is Musachi's tawaramusubi!
Everyone raved about it, so I'm looking forward to eating it!
I'm off to eat!
We're all set!
I'll do my best!
See you later!
Hiroshima!
Hare Toki albaikerie at jori.co.jp
Haretoki Tupperware is at jori.co.jp
Haretoki's twitter is haretoki
We know Haretoki too!
And we have an official twitter!
The account is haretoki1422.
I'll be tweeting important information from the show!
Please join us!
This is an announcement from the perfect domestic super-tokimeki ceilidh!
Al-chan, we'll be on our way soon.
Okay, I'll be there.
Today's super-toki-meki promotional letter
How to Rock on HALL TOUR 2023
You're too cute and adorable!
Thank you very much for coming to the show.
Thank you very much!
I'm Hitoka Sakai, aka Hito-chan!
Bye bye!
Please listen to what I'm going to say until the end.
Understood?
Yes!
Before the show begins.
I have a few words of caution and a favor to ask of our guests.
The show will start soon.
Everyone...
Are you ready to have fun?
Today, too...
Will you tell our members they're cute?
Thank you! We'll send you lots of love too!
Just wait a little longer!
Bye bye!
Yes, perfect!
Okay, well, thank you very much.
Thank you!
Churia! Hitoko! Maruko! Akki! Yuri!
Super thrilling advertisement
Rock on!
Let's go for it!
Yes, please everyone!
Let's go!
Bye-bye!
Let's go.
Okay.
Is there sound?
No sound.
Let's try it again.
Here we go.
Oh!
That's a nice sound.
That's a good sound.
My hands are hot.My hands are hot.
Hands are hot
Hands hot.
I'll go twice.
First time in isolation.
How's the bangs coming?
Please take pretty pictures, everyone. I'll be there soon.
Congratulations, Mr. Oh!
Congratulations, Mr. Oku!
Good day to you, see you again.
★Thank you, Hiroshima Park ★Thank you, Hiroshima Park ★Thank you, Hiroshima Park ★Thank you, Hiroshima Park
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Hiroshima is over.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So today was the Hiroshima concert.
It was wonderful.
The diary was amazing.
Everyone was amazing.
I was sweating so much during the rock 'n' free time,
It was great. We were so cute.
We were as embarrassed as the rest of them.
It was so far away, it was like a rush to get to Berlin.
It was fun.
It was so much fun.
It was amazing.
It was a lot of fun.
I want to come again.
If you come, will you come?
Please come to the stage in Hiroshima.
I want to increase the number.
I want to double the number.
More and more.
I will do my best.
I will come back again.
Next stop: Sendai.
I will do my best.
See you soon.
Okay, I will.
Please wait.
This might be the first time since the show ended.
I'll have to put my hands on it.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm good.
You want some?
I don't eat.
Bon appétit.
It's too good.
Even better.
This is too good.
Too good!
With such care!
Here it is!
Wait a minute!
What? Look at his face.
Delicious.
It's so good!
Purdue's Lars Gorilla.
I don't know why, but when I smile, it's as if the world is shining.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying, somewhere I'll get wet again and won't get cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart
They guide me along the way
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
I'll try to smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, spilling every tear
I'll wear a rainbow dress
LaLaLaLa...
Please subscribe to our channel!